MAZHAR IQBAL

Student of BBA, Namal Business School Namal College, Mianwali, Pakistan





OBJECTIVE

I am student of Namal College (An affiliated College of University of Engineering & Technology Lahore, Pakistan). I am working in NSSI (Namal Society for Social Impact) to create demonstrative social impact in education and health for society. My aim is to specialize in the field of Marketing & Entrepreneurship.

EDUCATION

Namal College, Mianwali (University of Engineering & Technology, Lahore) Student

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

Board of Intermediate & Secondary Education, Rawalpindi (2016)

Intermediate (Pre-Engineering)

Board of Intermediate & Secondary Education, Sargodha (2014)

Matriculation (Science)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Entrepreneur (2016-2017)

Work at "Haidral Fabrics" to learn business and entrepreneurial skills.

Teacher Assistant (2017-2018)

Business Mathematics teacher assistant for junior student.

Namal Society for Social Impact

(2017-Present)

Volunteer Teacher: Work as volunteer to teach native under privileged students.

Namal Idea Club (2018-Present)

• **Head of Entrepreneurship Chapter:** To families' the Students with new ideas and entrepreneurial skills.

Namal Adventure Club (2017-2018)

• Marketing Manager: To advertise trips and events in University.

SOFT & TECHNICAL

Soft Skill: Entrepreneurial, Public Speaking, Leadership & Management

Computer Tools: Microsoft (Word, PowerPoint, Excel), Content Creation, Scratch, Online Marketing, HTML

Operating Tool: Windows, Java, Android

REFRENCES

Available on Request